So, now that we understand
因此，现在我们了解了
information visualization and information visualization systems,
信息可视化和信息可视化系统，
we can start to use them to visualize data held in databases,
我们可以开始使用它们来可视化数据库中保存的数据
and we can use them in concert with data mining.
，我们可以将它们与数据挖掘结合使用。
So, often, when we visualize data,
所以，通常，当我们
data for our own purposes and gain insight into the data.
对数据进行可视化时，数据将来自数据库，如果在交互式可视化会话期间，我们试图为自己的目的调查数据并深入了解数据，这将是非常有用和有效的。
If we can connect the tools for visualization into queries to that database,
如果我们可以将用于可视化的工具连接到该数据库中，以
so that it's easier to dig deeper into the data directly.
便更容易直接深入挖掘数据。
So, there are databases that support this.
所以，有数据库支持这一点。
Often, modern databases support OLAP processing,
通常，现代数据库支持 OLAP 处理，
Online Analytical Processing which basically allows
在线分析处理，基本上允许
them to be accessed over the web using standard protocols.
使用标准协议通过 Web 访问它们。
Conceptually, a good mental model for the data is this data cube metaphor.
从概念上讲，数据的一个很好的心理模型就是这个数据多维数据集的隐喻。
If you have for example, a sales database that
例如，如果您有一个销售数据库，该数据库
represents the amount of sales on a given date,
表示给定日期
of a given product at a given location,
的给定产品在给定位置的销售额，
then you can think of the keys to that dataset, the date,
那么您可以想到该数据集的关键字、日期、
the product and location has dimensions of for example a cube here.
产品和位置的维度，例如此处的立方体。
So, each row of this data corresponds to a cell in this dataset.
因此，此数据的每一行对应于此数据集中的一个单元格。
So if the date is the horizontal axis,
因此，如果日期是水平轴，
the product is the vertical axis,
产品是垂直轴，
and the location is the depth axis in this cube,
位置是这个立方体中的深度轴，
then you've got three coordinates and that gives you a particular cell in
那么你有三个坐标，这给你一个特定的单元格在
this cube and that cell will represent the amount
这个立方体，该单元格将表示该
of sales at that date of that product at that location.
产品的该日期的销售额在那个位置。
The challenge is going to be taking this dataset and visualizing it.
面临的挑战是获取这个数据集并将其视觉化。
I'm using an example of a cube with
我用一个有
three dimensions and we used to perceiving three dimensions,
三维度的立方体的例子，我们曾
but we perceive three dimensions by projecting it
经感知到三维，但是我们通过
into two dimensions and looking at that.
将它投射成两个维度来感知三维度，然后看到它。
In real-world applications you're going to have many more keys
在现实世界的应用程序中，您将拥有更多的密钥，
and this data cube is actually a data hypercube and you'll have
这个数据多维数据集实际上是一个数据超
many more than just three dimensions of data and
多维数据集，并且您将拥有更多的不仅仅
the challenge is going to be taking this high dimensional data space,
是三维数据，挑战将是占用这个高维数据空间，
this data hypercube and then finding the appropriate two dimensions in
这个数据超立方体，然后找到适当的两个维度
which to investigate and then you can always add
进行调查，然后您始终可以添加
more dimensions as glyphs or other visualization tools.
更多维度作为字形或其他可视化工具。
So, the way we're going to reduce
所以，我们减少数据
the dimensions of the dataset is going to be largely with
集维度的方式主要是
data aggregation and there's a large number of
数据聚合，并且有大量基于数据聚
database visualization tools based on data aggregation.
合的数据库可视化工具。
The common ones like Tableau or SAP's
常见的表（如 Tableau 或 SAP 的
Lumina or even the pivot tables that are available in Microsoft Excel
Lumina），甚至是 Microsoft Excel 中提供的透视表，
or are based on data aggregation as a way of simplifying a dataset and
或者基于数据聚合作为
reducing the dimensions of variation by providing summaries of the data.
通过提供数据摘要来简化数据集和减少变异维度的一种方法。
So, for example, here's some data we're plotting some quantitative value
所以，例如，这里有一些数据，我们正在
vertically as we change some other quantitative value horizontally, you got that?
垂直绘制一些定量值，因为我们水平改变了一些其他的定量值，你明白了吗？ 这里
An independent variable here and a dependent variable here.
是一个独立的变量，这里是一个依赖变量。
This is a two-dimensional plot,
这是一个二维图，
we could always project this onto a one-dimensional axis,
我们总是可以把它投影到一维轴上
and we can also summarize this data.
，我们也可以汇总这些数据。
These would be values,
这些值将是值，
these would be measures,
这些将是测量值，
a single value by representing it by the mean value or the maximum value,
通过以平均值或最大值、最
the minimum value or the sum of these values.
小值或这些值的总和来表示它，跨一个轴更改为单个值。
The mean is just going to be the sum divided by all the values of the dimension.
平均值只是总和除以维度的所有值。
The dimension of the dimension.
维度的维度。
So, we have various operators,
所以，我们有各种运算符，
some mean, median, minimum, maximum,
一些平均值，中位数，最小值，最大值，
there's other statistical operators like standard deviation or variance or
还有其他统计运算符，如标准差或方差或
other characteristics you can use that will
其他特征，你可以使用它们
simplify data and basically remove one dimension.
简化数据并基本上删除一个维度。
In this case, removing the change in value over
在这种情况下，将
one dimension to a single value over no dimension.
一个维度上的值更改移除为无维度的单个值。
We can also convert quantitative continuous data
我们还可以将定量连续数据
into quantitative-discrete data or ordinal or nominal data,
转换为定量离散数据或序数或标称数据，
and the count function does that.
并且计数函数可以做到这一点。
For example, if we have these blue red and green data points,
例如，如果我们有这些蓝色和绿色的数据点，
there's three categories here,
这里有三个类别，
they're being plotted over two-dimensional area that's
它们被绘制在二维区域上，它们
going to represent continuous quantitative data horizontally and vertically.
将以水平和垂直方式表示连续的定量数据。
We can then remove those axes and just have a single axis representing the count,
然后，我们可以删除这些轴，只有一个表示计数、
the number of blue items,
蓝色项目数量、
the number of red items and the number of green items.
红色项目数量和绿色项目数量的轴。
That reduces the dimensionality of this dataset from varying over two dimensions with
这
a third category into just a category over essentially one dimension.
样可以将此数据集的维度从两个维度变化（第三个类别）降低为基本上一个维度的类别。
Finally, there's binning.
最后，还有包装。
Binning is a discretization method that converts a quantitative continuous data
Binning 是一种离散化方法，根据
into quantitative discrete data or ordinal or nominal data depending on how you use it.
您的使用方式，将定量连续数据转换为定量离散数据或序数或标称数据。
For example, we may have our continuous function,
例如，我们可能有我们的连续功能，
these are values that are varying over a single dimension.
这些值在单个维度上变化。
we can discretize this dimension.
我们可以使这个维度离散，而不是在连续维度上连续表示这些值。
Then we have our quantitative variable that's being sampled
然后我们有我们的定量变量，它在
on four regions and represented by in this case,
四个区域上被采样，在这种情况下，
the mean value over those four bin areas.
表示为这四个区域的平均值。
So, we're doing a projection operator in
所以，在
this case over four areas instead of over the single area.
这种情况下，我们正在做一个投影运算符，在四个区域，而不是在单个区域。
But again, that does reduce the dimensionality of the dataset.
但同样，这确实会降低数据集的维度。
Finally, we can use this to create a histogram.
最后，我们可以用它来创建一个直方图。
A histogram is binning, in this case,
在这种情况下，直方图是在
in the vertical direction instead of the horizontal direction.
垂直方向而不是水平方向上进行分组。
So, instead of having bins over the dimension,
所以，而不
you are having bins over the value that you're plotting over that dimension.
是在维度上有条柱，而是在您在该维度上绘制的值上有条柱。
In this case, we've separated the values into an A,
在这种情况下，我们将这些值分为 A、
B, C, D and E range.
B、C、D 和 E 范围。
Then we're adding up all the values in the A range,
然后我们将 A 范围中的所有值，
all the values in the B range,
B 范围中的所有值，
all the values in the C range,
C 范围中的所有值，以
and all the values in the D range and just plotting those sums.
及 D 范围中的所有值，然后只绘制这些总和。
There's no values in the E range so,
E 范围内没
there would be zero for the E range.
有值，因此 E 范围将有零。
So, this histogram, when you choose these buckets,
所以，这
a continuous variable into discrete categories of a continuous variable.
个直方图，当你选择这些桶时，这些条柱的大小，给你数据的其他特征，这些特征可以降低数据的维度，或者至少将连续变量减少为连续变量的离散类别。
So, our data cubes can use these aggregation operations to simplify
因此，我们的数据多维数据集可以使用这些聚合操作来简化数据
a dataset and that provides a useful tool for investigating the dataset.
集，并为调查数据集提供了一个有用的工具。
So for example, we can take our data cube in this case,
例如，我们可以在这种情况下采用我们的数据立方体，
it has location horizontally,
它具有水平位置，
products vertically and time in depth.
产品垂直和时间深度。
If we for example,
例如，如果我们
if we want to look at all of our sales of tea, coffee,
想查看我们在不同
espresso or other products over time at different times,
时间的茶叶、咖啡、浓缩咖啡或其他产品的销售情况，
but we don't care about the location,
但我们不关心位置，
then we can project this data cube
那么我们可以将这个数据立方体
into basically this square region, this two-dimensional region.
投射到基本上这个正方形区域，这个二维区域。
So this is a two-dimensional projection that's summing up all of
所以这是一个二维投影，它总结了给定
the sales at any given time of a given product regardless of location.
产品的任何给定时间的所有销售额，无论位置如何。
So it's summing them up over all the locations and
所以它
that projection gives us something we can then visualize.
将它们总结到所有位置，投影给了我们一些我们可以看到的东西。
We can further summarize that projecting this two-dimensional data cube into
我们可以进一步总结一下，
a one-dimensional data cube by summing in this case, over product.
通过在这种情况下总结，将这个二维数据立方投影到一维数据立方体中，在产品上进行总结。
We don't care about the differences of the products.
我们不关心产品的差异。
If we don't want to differentiate the product,
如果我们不想区分产品，
we can aggregate the product axis sum over that,
我们可以汇总产品轴的总
and now we have a one-dimensional basically,
和，现在我们基本上有一个一维的，
just a list of numbers that tells us the amount of sales for the first quarter,
只是一个数字列表，告诉我们第一季度，第
second quarter, third quarter or fourth quarter.
二季度，第三季度或第四季度的销售额。
If we don't care about the time,
如果我们不关心时间，
then we can just look at the total sales over a given amount of time,
那么我们可以查看给定时间内的总销售额，在给定的
over a given set of products,
一组产品上，在给
over a given set of locations,
定的位置，
add all those up and that gives us a zero-dimensional data cube here.
将所有这些添加起来，这给了我们一个零维数据的立方体。
So, here's an example using Tableau to show how
因此，下面是一个使用 Tableau 的示例，显示如何将
aggregations are used for data cube operations.
聚合用于数据多维数据集操作。
Here we have some dimensions of our data.
在这里，我们有我们的数据的一些维度。 这
The data is collected over ten years.
些数据是在十年内收集的。
So we have separate data by year and over a variety of different countries.
因此，我们有不同的年份和不同的国家的单独数据。
Then we've got the,
然后，我们得到了，
what I'm showing here is our standard method for plotting population logarithmically,
我在这里展示的是我们的标准方法，用于对
horizontally, over life expectancy vertically.
数，水平，在预期寿命上以垂直方式绘制人口。
You'll see that we're averaging the data and we have a single data point.
你会看到，我们正在对数据进行平均化，我们有一个数据点。
We basically have a zero-dimensional data,
我们基本上有一个零维数据，所有
it's all being projected to a single point
这些数据都被投影到一个点，
because we're averaging over all these dimensions.
因为我们在所有这些维度上进行平均化。
Specifically at the time dimension over all the years that we
特别是在我们
have data and over all the countries that we have data.
拥有数据的所有年份的时间维度和我们拥有数据的所有国家。
If we want to disaggregate this data,
如果我们想分解这
then we can do that by basically dragging into this marks area.
些数据，那么我们可以通过基本上拖到这个标记区域来做到这一点。
For example, country.
例如，国家。
Now, we spread out the data,
现在，我们分散数据，
each one of these data points represents
这些数据点中的每个数据点代表
a different country that these averages are just averages over
一个不同的国家，这些平均数只是
the year that the data's collected on and add over the country and the region.
数据收集到的一年中的平均值，并在国家和地区上添加。
We can further disaggregate over the year and we get
我们可以在一年中进一步分类，我们得到
this plot which shows you each country that's how it's changing over the year.
这个情节，它显示了每个国家是如何在一年中变化的。
If we want to see correspondences between countries,
如果我们想看到
then I can drag the country into color so that each country gets its own color.
国家之间的对应，那么我可以把国家拖到颜色，让每个国家都有自己的颜色。
So you can see how the colors,
所以你可以看到颜色如何，
you can use the color to follow the country over the years it's been disaggregated.
你可以使用颜色跟随这个国家多年来它被分类。
We can start adding more and more dimensions from our data cube into this visualization.
我们可以开始从我们的数据多维数据集中添加越来越多的维度到这个可视化。
So, when you're looking at an individual cell of these different forms of data cubes,
因此，当您查看这些不同形式的数据多维数据集的单个单元格时，
you can work from a less detailed view to a more detailed view.
您可以从不太详细的视图到更详细的视图。 对
A single cube when it's averaged,
单个立方体进行平均时，
could represent a range of products,
可以表示产品
a range of locations,
范围、位置范
a range of times or it could represent
围、时间范围，也可以
the values in a specific location at a specific time.
表示特定时间特定位置的值。
In its disaggregated form it's representing an actual data point.
在其分类形式中，它代表了一个实际的数据点。
In its aggregated form,
在其聚合形式中，
it's representing an aggregate of the values over these ranges.
它表示这些范围内的值的聚合。
So, this could be the total sales of all products,
所以，这可能是所有产品的总销售额，
over all markets, over all time.
在所有市场，在所有时间。
Then you can start to drill down to these details by basically focusing for example,
然后，您可以开始深入了解这些详细信息，例如，基本上专注
or on a particular product,
于特定的时间实例、特定产品
or on a particular type.
或特定类型。
Each time you do that,
每次执行此操作时，
you're replacing an aggregated dimension where you have
您都将使用
these dimensions with a specific product or a specific data point along that dimension,
特定产品或沿该维度的特定数据点（沿该维度的特定
a specific coordinate along that dimension.
坐标）替换一个聚合维度，其中包含一个表示这些维度的范围的单个值。
So by doing that,
因此，通过这样做，
this data cube approach allows you while you're performing
这种数据多维数据集方法可以让
your visualization to be able to drill down in the details
您在执行可视化时能够深入了解详细信息
and tend to back out into more summary views.
并倾向于回溯到更多的摘要视图。